<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>List Page on OpenEMR</title>
    <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in List Page on OpenEMR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>OpenEMR Foundation, Inc</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.open-emr.org/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR Announces Sponsorship of HealthHacks 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/sponsoring-healthhacks-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/sponsoring-healthhacks-2018/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenEMR announced for the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.open-emr.org/blog/success-at-healthhacks-2017/&#34;&gt;second year&lt;/a&gt; in a row it will be a sponsor of Virginia Commonwealth Universities (VCU) &lt;a href=&#34;https://healthhacks.vcu.edu&#34;&gt;HealthHacks&lt;/a&gt; event; a 24-hour hackathon bringing together students of engineering, medicine, and computer sciences.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Features to Look For in Your Medical Practice Management Software</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/7-features-to-look-for-in-your-medical-practice-management-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/7-features-to-look-for-in-your-medical-practice-management-software/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When searching for, it is important to look for some specific key features that enable your team to take full advantage of the platform.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR Offers a Panel of Turn-Key Solutions with Amazon&#39;s Cloud Services</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-offers-panel-of-turn-key-solutions-with-amazons-cloud-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-offers-panel-of-turn-key-solutions-with-amazons-cloud-services/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenEMR now offers a full panel of easy to install packages on Amazon’s Cloud Services platform, AWS.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR Cloud Standard Edition Now Available in AWS Marketplace</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-cloud-standard-edition-now-available-in-aws-marketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-cloud-standard-edition-now-available-in-aws-marketplace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenEMR Cloud Standard is the first EHR in the Amazon Marketplace directly aimed at domestic US providers.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR Version 5.0.1 Released: Ushers in Golden Age for OpenEMR</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-version-501-released-ushers-in-golden-age-for-openemr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-version-501-released-ushers-in-golden-age-for-openemr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The amount of new features and improvements in this new release of OpenEMR is simply astounding and showcases the strengths, diversity, talents, commitment, productivity, and good will of the thriving OpenEMR community.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR, A Great Long Term Choice</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/great-long-term-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/great-long-term-choice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Choosing a free and open source EMR with a history of success around the world is a great move for those looking to avoid vendor lock-in. As a mature project with a vibrant community, OpenEMR is a great choice for the long term.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR Medical Image Viewer</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/medical-image-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/medical-image-viewer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A team of software engineers within our community recently built the first major medical imaging feature into the system. Given a DICOM file in a patient chart, users can now utilize an easy-to-use medical image visualizer.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Docker</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/embracing-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/embracing-docker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenEMR remains in the midst of its Docker revolution with big plans for the future, including utilizing docker images to support medical record interoperability with Fast Healthcare Interoperability Resources, patient data analytics with Shiny R, and patient imaging picture archiving and communication system integration with an Orthanc Digital Imaging and Communications in Medicine (DICOM) server.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accepting Donations on OpenCollective</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/accepting-donations-on-opencollective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/accepting-donations-on-opencollective/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Donations speed up and improve the outcome of community requests. It is not simply the case that donating funds to our volunteer developers will motivate us to move faster or produce better results. Historically, hiring trusted development partners and supplying funds to our development teams have proved to move projects to the finish line.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Students Showcase Solutions for Developing Nations at HealthHacks 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/success-at-healthhacks-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/success-at-healthhacks-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Virginia Commonwealth University&amp;rsquo;s School of Engineering held their second annual HealthHacks event November 3rd and 4th; OpenEMR was not only a sponsor of the event, but also sent me as a representative offering mentorship to the nearly 130 students participating in the event. Here is my takeaway from this successful event.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR at WONCA SAR</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-at-wonca-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-at-wonca-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Matthew Vita, a software developer and project administrator for OpenEMR and Dr. Andre Millet, a physician and medical officer for OpenEMR were pleased to present “Improving Outpatient and Inpatient Care with the OpenEMR Platform” at WONCA South Asia Region 2017.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Maria, Puerto Rico, and the success of OpenEMR customers</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/hurricane-maria-puerto-rico-openemr-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/hurricane-maria-puerto-rico-openemr-success/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Some had power or a generator, most had no internet access, but all had OpenEMR with individualized customization installed on HITECH Compliance MD-Guardian Server.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR and the 2017 VCU HealthHacks</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/healthhacks-at-vcu-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/healthhacks-at-vcu-2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenEMR is proud to be a contributing sponsor of the 2017 HealthHacks at VCU, a 24-hour event at Virginia Commonwealth University involving engineering, medical, and computer science students coming together to problem solve and innovate on current unmet medical needs.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMR Announces Initial Availability of OpenEMR Cloud on AWS</title>
      <link>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-announces-initial-availability-of-openemr-cloud-on-aws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.open-emr.org/blog/openemr-announces-initial-availability-of-openemr-cloud-on-aws/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenEMR has joined with industry leading Amazon Web Services to implement and deliver OpenEMR Cloud to healthcare provider practices and institutions throughout the world
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>